{
    "subject": "resource/Sivakorn_Pu-Udom",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Thai_football_referees",
    "human_readable": "Sivakorn Pu-Udom is about Thai football referees.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9371122121810913,
            "question": "What are some challenges faced by Thai football referees like Sivakorn Pu-Udom?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.922410249710083,
            "question": "What role does Sivakorn Pu-Udom have in Thai football?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9187543988227844,
            "question": "What is the significance of Sivakorn Pu-Udom's work in Thai football?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9065217971801758,
            "question": "Is Sivakorn Pu-Udom involved in Thai sports?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7762648463249207,
            "question": "How does Sivakorn Pu-Udom contribute to the fairness of Thai football matches?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7608107328414917,
            "question": "Does Sivakorn Pu-Udom have any influence on the rules and regulations of Thai football?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7548068761825562,
            "question": "What kind of sporting events does Sivakorn Pu-Udom officiate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7507115602493286,
            "question": "Who is Sivakorn Pu-Udom?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6258636116981506,
            "question": "What is Sivakorn Pu-Udom known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.472432404756546,
            "question": "Are there any notable achievements associated with Sivakorn Pu-Udom's career?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sivakorn Pu-Udom is about Thai football referees.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1800_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Sivakorn Pu-Udom known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1800_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Sivakorn Pu-Udom?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1800_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of sporting events does Sivakorn Pu-Udom officiate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1800_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1800_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1800_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1800_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1800_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1800_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1800_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1800_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1800_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1800_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1800_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Sivakorn Pu-Udom, a Thai football referee. They mention his refereeing in various leagues and competitions in Thailand and China, as well as his status as a FIFA elite-class referee. This supports the statement that Sivakorn Pu-Udom is involved with Thai football referees."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}